<org.tdod.ether.taimpl.cosmos.DefaultRoomDescriptions>
  <__roomDescriptions>
    <entry>
      <int>-31</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the weapon shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-32</int>
      <string>You are now inside the weapon shop, where you may purchase various
weapons to use for sparring in the arena or for personal defense from the
denizens of the dungeons. The shop keeper sits on a high stool behind a
tall counter along the west wall. The exit is to the northeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-29</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-30</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into a weapon shop to the southwest,
and to the town&apos;s southern plaza to the northeast. Large old trees line the
path and lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-27</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the south plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-28</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the south end of town surrounded
by shade trees. A path to the north leads to a plaza in the northern end of
town. To the southwest, a well trodden path leads to what appears to be a
weapon shop. A third path to the southeast leads to the docks.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-25</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-26</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into an open plaza to the northwest,
and to the docks on the great lake to the southeast. Large old trees line
the path and lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-23</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on the docks.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-24</int>
      <string>You are standing on the docks. The water from the lake laps quietly against
the docks making the peaceful scene on the lake all that more serene. A path
leads towards a large open plaza to the northwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-21</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on the docks.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-22</int>
      <string>You are standing on the docks. The water from the lake laps quietly against
the docks making the peaceful scene on the lake all that more serene. An
ornately carved marble archway exits through the town wall to the south into
the guild hall.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-19</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the south plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-20</int>
      <string>You are standing at the south end of a large open plaza surrounded
by shade trees as well as assorted flowering shrubs and hedges who&apos;s
scent wafts through the warm, dry air. To the west stands the town&apos;s
armor shop. The weapon shop lies to the east. There is a magic shop
to the south. To the north lies the other half of the plaza and to
the southwest lies the town&apos;s outer gate.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-17</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the magic shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-18</int>
      <string>You&apos;re standing in a warm, dimly lit shop where various magical items
are bought and sold by a shrewd mage in crimson robes with an air of
power and complete confidence about him. He doesn&apos;t look like someone
whose spells you&apos;d like to be on the wrong end of. The sweet scent of
incense drifts in from a workroom in the rear of the shop. The exit is
to the north.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-16</int>
      <string>You have entered the town guild hall, where one may seek the training
neccessary to refine your combat and spell skills. This building is
also a center of learning where the ancient art of sorcery is taught
to those with the intelligence and skill to wield it effectively. Sages,
wizards, and masters-at-arms rush about on errands or to and from
training sessions. Ornately carved marble archways exit to the north and
south, and a wide stone staircase leads downward.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-15</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the guild hall.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-14</int>
      <string>You are now inside the armor shop, where you may aquire different
sorts of armor and protective gear to guard yourself against the blows
of your opponents in the arena, or from the various non-human foes to be
found in the dungeons beneath the town. The shop keeper sits on a high
behind a worn counter along the south wall, eyeing you warily. The exit
is to the east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-13</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the armor shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-12</int>
      <string>You are now inside the weapon shop, where you may purchase various
weapons to use for sparring in the arena or for personal defense from
the denizens of the dungeons. The shop keeper sits on a high stool
behind a tall counter along the south wall. The exit is to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-11</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the weapon shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-10</int>
      <string>You are in the village tavern. The smoke from the many oil lamps
decrease visibility to your imediate surroundings, and the wavering
light they cast about the room leaves many shadows and unlit corners.
There are several tables about the room, where the tavern&apos;s patrons
eat, drink, and generally enjoy themselves. The bar stands along the
north wall and a door to the kitchen lies to the northeast. A large,
full length mirror adorns the west wall. The only visible exits lie
up a steep wooden ladder near the rear of the room, and out into the
north plaza to the southwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-9</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the tavern.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-8</int>
      <string>You are now in the main entry hall of a great temple. Huge black
marble columns veined with platinum stretch to the ceiling some 100&apos;
overhead. The paterns in the tile floor are so ornate and complex as to
be nearly impossible to follow or comprehend. Many black silk tapestries
depicting various scenes of a religious or magical nature block your view
into the many other areas of the temple. Blue robed priests and acolytes
move here and there going about their daily duties. The exit is to the
east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-7</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the temple.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-6</int>
      <string>You are now inside the equipment shop, where one may purchase supplies
and provisions essential to survival in the dungeons or the wilderness.
The shop keeper sits on a tall stool behind a counter along the north
wall, eyeing you warily. The exit is to the southeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-5</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the equipment shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-4</int>
      <string>You now stand inside the gates of the village&apos;s most noteworthy and
notorious point of interest, the arena. The charred and stained stone
walls and scattered bits of bone, armor, and weaponry lying among the
debris on the packed earthen floor. A huge brass gong hangs at the center
of the arena suspended on a framework made of the bones of some of the
less fortunate of the arena&apos;s combatants. To the south is a wide stone
staircase leading down to the dungeon gate. The exit through the arena
gates is to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-3</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the arena.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-2</int>
      <string>You are standing at the north end of a large open plaza surrounded
by shade trees as well as assorted flowering shrubs and hedges whose
scent wafts through the warm, dry air. To the west stands an ornate
temple adorned with ornate stone and brass architecture. A quaint little
shop lies to the northwest, and a dimly lit, smokey little tavern to the
northeast. To the east lay the huge wrought iron gates of the arena. To
north is the town guild hall. The other half of the plaza lies to the
south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-1</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the north plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-61</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-62</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into an open plaza to the north,
and to the town&apos;s temple to the south. Large old trees line the path and
lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-63</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the temple.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-64</int>
      <string>You are now in the main entry hall of a great temple. Huge black
marble columns veined with platinum stretch to the ceiling some 100&apos;
overhead. The paterns in the tile floor are so ornate and complex as to
be nearly impossible to follow or comprehend. Many black silk tapestries
depicting various scenes of a religious or magical nature block your view
into the many other areas of the temple. Blue robed priests and acolytes
move here and there going about their duties. The exit is to the north.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-57</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-58</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into an open plaza to the west,
and to the armor shop to the east. Large old trees line the path and
lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-59</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the armor shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-60</int>
      <string>You are now inside the armor shop, where you may aquire different sorts
of armor and protective gear to guard yourself against the blows of your
opponents in the arena, or from the various non-human foes to be found
in the dungeons near the town. The shop keeper sits on a high stool
behind a worn counter along the east wall, eyeing you warily. The exit
is to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-53</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-54</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into an open plaza to the south,
and to the town&apos;s arena to the north. Large old trees line the path and
lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-55</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the arena.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-56</int>
      <string>You now stand inside the gates of the town&apos;s arena. The charred and
stained stone walls and scattered bits of bone, armor, and weaponry
lying among the debris on the packed earthen floor. A huge bronze
gong hangs at the center of the arena suspended on a framework made
of the bones of some of the less fortunate of the arena&apos;s combatants.
The exit through the arena gates is to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-49</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-50</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into open plazas to the east and
west. Large old trees line the path and lend shade and birdsong to this
quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-51</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the east plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-52</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the east end of town surrounded
by shade trees. A well trodden path to the east leads to an armor shop. To
the west, another well used path leads to an open plaza in the northern end
of town. A third path to the south leads to towns temple, and a fourth path
leads to the town&apos;s arena.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-46</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into a magic shop to the north and,
to the town&apos;s northern plaza to the south. Large old trees line the path
and lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-45</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-48</int>
      <string>You&apos;re standing in a warm, dimly lit shop where various magical items
are bought and sold by a shrewd mage in crimson robes with an air of
power and complete confidence about him. He doesn&apos;t look like someone
whose spells you&apos;d like to be on the wrong end of. The sweet scent of
incense drifts in from a workroom in the rear of the shop. The exit is
to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-47</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the magic shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-42</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into an equipment shop to the west,
and to the town&apos;s northern plaza to the east. Large old trees line the path
and lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-41</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-44</int>
      <string>You are now inside the equipment shop, where one may purchase supplies
and provisions essential to survival in the dungeons or the wilderness.
The shop keeper sits on a tall stool behind a counter along the west
wall, eyeing you warily. The exit is to the east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-43</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the equipment shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-38</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into the town&apos;s inn to the southwest,
and to the town&apos;s northern plaza to the northeast. Large old trees line the
path and lend shade and birdsong to this quaint little town. There is a
large rusty grate here which leads down into the town sewers.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-37</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-40</int>
      <string>You are in the town&apos;s inn. The smoke from the many oil lamps decrease
visibility to your imediate surroundings, and the wavering light they
cast about the room leaves many shadows and unlit corners. There are
several tables about the room, where the inn&apos;s patrons eat, drink, and
generally enjoy themselves. The bar stands along the north wall and a
door to the kitchen lies to the southwest, and a staircase leads up to
the inn&apos;s rooms. The only visibile exit lies to the northeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-39</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the inn.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-34</int>
      <string>You are standing on a path that leads into open plazas to the north and
south. Large old trees line the path and lend shade and birdsong to this
quaint little town.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-33</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a path.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-36</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the north end of town surrounded
by shade trees. A path to the east leads to a plaza in the eastern end of
town. To the west, a well trodden path leads to town&apos;s equipment shop. A
third path to the south leads to a plaza in the southern end of town, and
a fourth path leads to an inn to the southwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-35</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the north plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-91</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the weapon shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-92</int>
      <string>You are now inside the weapon shop, where you may purchase various
weapons to use for sparring in the arena or for personal defense from
the denizens of the dungeons. The shop keeper sits on a high stool
behind a tall counter along the south wall. A stone archway lies to
the to the northwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-89</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the armor shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-90</int>
      <string>You are now inside the armor shop, where you may aquire different
sorts of armor and protective gear to guard yourself against the blows
of your opponents. The shop keeper sits on a high behind a worn counter
along the west wall, eyeing you warily. A stone archway lies to the to
the northeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-95</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-96</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk is anchored against the trunk of a
huge tree to the south, and continues north. There is a round hole
in the platform near the tree trunk which leads down to some large
branches which appear climbable.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-93</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the arena.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-94</int>
      <string>You are standing in an enormous natural cavern of dark reddish stone.
The charred and stained walls and stonework floor tell of battles
ancient and recent that have been fought in this place of death. The
floor and walls of this cavern give off noticable heat. A huge iron
gong hangs at the center of the arena suspended on a framework made
of the bones of demons and dragons. The exit through a huge stone
archway is to the southwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-83</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the tavern.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-84</int>
      <string>You are in the tavern. The smoke from the many oil lamps decreases
visibility to your imediate surroundings, and the wavering light they
cast about the room leaves many shadows and unlit corners. There are
several tables about the room, where the tavern&apos;s rowdy patrons,
primarily dwarves, gnomes, and an occasional goblin make themselves at
home. The bar stands along the north wall and a door to the kitchen
lies to the west. The only visibile exit lies to the southeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-81</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the temple.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-82</int>
      <string>You are now in the main entry hall of a great temple. Huge reddish
stone columns stretch to the ceiling some 50&apos; overhead. The stone floor
is made up of intricately engraved flagstones. Heavy cloth tapestries
depicting various scenes of dwarven religious cerimonies block your view
into the other areas of the temple. Grey robed priests and acolytes
move here and there going about their daily duties. An ornate archway
exits to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-87</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the equipment shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-88</int>
      <string>You are now inside the equipment shop, where one may purchase supplies
and provisions essential to survival in the dungeons or the wilderness.
The shop keeper sits on a tall stool behind a counter along the west
wall, eyeing you warily. A stone archway lies to the to the southeast.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-85</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the magic shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-86</int>
      <string>You&apos;re standing in a warm, dimly lit shop where various magical items
are bought and sold by a shrewd mage in crimson robes with an air of
power and complete confidence about him. He doesn&apos;t look like someone
whose spells you&apos;d like to be on the wrong end of. The sweet scent of
incense drifts in from a workroom in the rear of the shop. A stone
archway lies to the to the northwest.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-76</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the northwest corner of an
enormous subterranean cavern. An ornate stone fountain of fine
craftsmanship stands in the center of the plaza. The gurgling fountain
fills you with a sense of peace and tranquility, and the cool air is
very still here. The plaza opens out into the town square to the
southeast. To the northeast, and northwest lie large stone archways
decorated with intricate stonework.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-75</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in an underground plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-74</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the southeast corner of an
enormous subterranean cavern. An ornate stone fountain of fine
craftsmanship stands in the center of the plaza. The gurgling fountain
fills you with a sense of peace and tranquility, and the cool air is
very still here. The plaza opens out into the town square to the
northwest. To the southeast lies a large stone archway decorated
with intricate stonework.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-73</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in an underground plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-80</int>
      <string>You have entered the town guild hall, where one may seek the training
neccessary to refine your combat and spell skills. This building is
also a center of learning where the ancient art of sorcery is taught
to those with the intelligence and skill to wield it effectively. Sages,
wizards, and masters-at-arms rush about on errands or to and from
training sessions. An ornately carved stone archway exits to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-79</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the guild hall.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-78</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the southwest corner of an
enormous subterranean cavern. An ornate stone fountain of fine
craftsmanship stands in the center of the plaza. The gurgling fountain
fills you with a sense of peace and tranquility, and the cool air is
very still here. The plaza opens out into the town square to the
northeast. To the northwest, southeast, and southwest lie large stone
archways decorated with intricate stonework.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-77</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in an underground plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-68</int>
      <string>You are standing at the entrance to the town vaults. The room is bare, and
fashioned from solid natural stone. On the south wall there is a huge iron
door, and an open window covered with iron bars. A richly dressed man in
the window looks at you expectantly. A wide stone staircase leads upward.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-67</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the town vaults.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-66</int>
      <string>You are in a private room above the tavern. The room is well furnished,
though not richly. A window in the northern wall affords a breathtaking
view of the great lake to the north of town. A steep wooden staircase
leads down through a trap door in the floor to the tavern common room.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-65</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in a private room.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-72</int>
      <string>You are standing in a large open plaza at the northeast corner of an
enormous subterranean cavern. An ornate stone fountain of fine
craftsmanship stands in the center of the plaza. The gurgling fountain
fills you with a sense of peace and tranquility, and the cool air is
very still here. The plaza opens out into the town square to the
southwest. To the north and east lie large stone archways decorated
with intricate stonework.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-71</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in an underground plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-70</int>
      <string>You are standing in the midst of a large open square in a subterranean
cavern. The vaulted ceiling rises high above your head into near dark.
The light from oil lamps spaced evenly about the square affords adequate
light. Plain stone benches of good workmanship line the outer edges of
the square. To the four primary compass points stand smooth stone walls
carved with detailed scenes depicting various aspects of dwarven life.
To the northeast, southeast, southwest, and northeast lie open plazas
surrounding ornate stone fountains.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-69</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the town square.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-121</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-122</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north. To the east lies
an ornately carved wooden archway.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-123</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the weapon shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-124</int>
      <string>You are now inside the weapon shop, where you may purchase various
weapons to use for personal defense from the denizens of the dungeons.
The shop keeper sits on a high stool behind a tall counter along the
east wall. The exit is to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-125</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the armor shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-126</int>
      <string>You are now inside the armor shop, where you may aquire different sorts
of armor and protective gear to guard yourself against the blows of your
opponents in the arenas, or from the various non-human foes to be found
in the dungeons. The shop keeper sits on a high stool behind a worn
counter along the north wall, eyeing you warily. The exit is to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-127</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-128</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. A large wooden platform lies to the south. The
catwalk continues north.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-113</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the northeast plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-114</int>
      <string>You are standing in the northeastern section of a large open square
platform made of wood. The platform is ringed by intricately carved
wooden railing. The trunk of a huge tree lies in the center of the
platform, and appears to be the central support for the surrounding
structure. The rest of the platform lies to the south and west, and
a wooden catwalk leads off into the trees to the east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-115</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-116</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. A large wooden platform lies to the west. The
catwalk continues east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-117</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-118</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north, east, and west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-119</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-120</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues south and west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-106</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. A large wooden platform lies to the north. The
catwalk continues south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-105</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-108</int>
      <string>You are standing in the southeastern section of a large open square
platform made of wood. The platform is ringed by intricately carved
wooden railing. The trunk of a huge tree lies in the center of the
platform, and appears to be the central support for the surrounding
structure. The rest of the platform lies to the north and west, and
a wooden catwalk leads off into the trees to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-107</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the southeast plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-110</int>
      <string>You are standing in the southwestern section of a large open square
platform made of wood. The platform is ringed by intricately carved
wooden railing. The trunk of a huge tree lies in the center of the
platform, and appears to be the central support for the surrounding
structure. The rest of the platform lies to the north and east, and
a wooden catwalk leads off into the trees to the west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-109</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the southwest plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-112</int>
      <string>You are standing in the northwestern section of a large open square
platform made of wood. The platform is ringed by intricately carved
wooden railing. The trunk of a huge tree lies in the center of the
platform, and appears to be the central support for the surrounding
structure. The rest of the platform lies to the south and east, and
a wooden catwalk leads off into the trees to the north.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-111</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the northwest plaza.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-98</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north and south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-97</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-100</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues south and west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-99</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-102</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues to the north and east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-101</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-104</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north and south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-103</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-150</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues south. To the north lies
an ornately carved wooden archway.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-149</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-148</int>
      <string>You&apos;re standing in a warm, dimly lit shop where various magical items
are bought and sold by a shrewd mage in crimson robes with an air of
power and complete confidence about him. He doesn&apos;t look like someone
whose spells you&apos;d like to be on the wrong end of. The sweet scent of
incense drifts in from a workroom in the rear of the shop. The exit is
to the north.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-147</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the magic shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-146</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north. To the south lies
an ornately carved wooden archway.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-145</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-135</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-136</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues east and south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-133</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the equipment shop.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-134</int>
      <string>You are now inside the equipment shop, where one may purchase supplies
and provisions essential to survival in the dungeons or the wilderness.
The shop keeper sits on a tall stool behind a counter along the west
wall, eyeing you warily. The exit is to the east.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-131</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-132</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues east. To the west lies
an ornately carved wooden archway.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-129</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-130</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues north, south, and west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-143</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-144</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues east and south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-141</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-142</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. A large wooden platform lies to the east. The
catwalk continues west.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-139</int>
      <string>You&apos;re in the tavern.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-140</int>
      <string>You are in the tavern. The smoke from the many oil lamps decreases
visibility to your imediate surroundings, and the wavering light they
cast about the room leaves many shadows and unlit corners. There are
several tables about the room, where the tavern&apos;s patrons,
primarily elves, and an occasional human make themselves at
home. The bar stands along the north wall and a door to the kitchen
lies to the east. The only visibile exit lies to the south.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-137</int>
      <string>You&apos;re on a catwalk.</string>
    </entry>
    <entry>
      <int>-138</int>
      <string>You are standing on a wooden catwalk suspended high in the trees of
a deep forest. The forest floor lies some fifty feet below you, and
is hidden in shadow. The catwalk continues west. To the north lies
an ornately carved wooden archway.</string>
    </entry>
  </__roomDescriptions>
</org.tdod.ether.taimpl.cosmos.DefaultRoomDescriptions>
